Alderfer, S. Stanley Arbitration Files 5576
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
S. Stanley Alderfer Arbitration Files
1946-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alderfer, S. Stanley
5576
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Files of the arbitrator Stanley S. Alderfer. Over four hundred decisions are included, many of which are multi-grievance cases.
5665288
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 30, 1989
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
Arranged chronologically by the year of the decision. Unless otherwise noted, the file contains only the award.
"A total of about 400 plus decisions are involved. Quite a number are multi-grievance cases, so about 500 grievance decisions are included."-- Stanley S. Alderfer
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial; Alderfer, S. Stanley
5665288
- Arbitration Decisions, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Standards Association representing Kaufmann Department Stores, Incorporated and Joseph Horne Company vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Local 237, Bartenders International League of America, 1946; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    6/7/46. Issue: Dues check-off.
  - Item 2: DeCamp Bus Lines and DeCamp Interstate Transit Company vs. Division 1317, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1946; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    6/6/46. Issue: Contract Modification.
  - Item 3: DeCamp Bus Lines and DeCamp Interstate Transit Company vs. Division 1317, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1946; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    6/20/46. Issue: Contract Modification.
  - Item 4: Thomas Flammer vs. Girard Warehousing Corporation, 1946; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    5/20/46. Issue: Dismissal.
  - Item 5: Francis H. Leggett and Company vs. Local 56, Meat and Cannery Workers Union, 1946; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 1)
    7/12/46. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    11/47. Issue: Arbitrability.
  - Item 2: John A. Roebling's Sons Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2110, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    3/8/47. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Discrimination.
  - Item 3: American Wire Fabrics Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3019, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4/30/47. Issue: Rates of Pay; Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 4: De Laval Steam Turbine Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    7/47. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 5: De Laval Steam Turbine Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    11/47. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 6: American Engineering Company vs. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 35, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    11/12/47. Issue: Vacation Pay.
  - Item 7: RCA Victor Division of Radio Corporation of America vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    12/47. Issue: Retroactive Pay.
  - Item 8: Sheridan Machine Company (Easton, Pennsylvania) vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 104, 1947; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 2)
    5/13/47. Issue: Reinstatement.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: RCA Victor Division of Radio Corporation of America vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 103, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    9/2/48. Issue: Classification of Job.
  - Item 2: Robert Lewis Company vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    6/10/48. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 3: Whitehall Cement Manufacturing Company vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers' International Union, Local 29, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    3/19/48. Issue: Discharge--Reinstatement.
  - Item 4: Hershey Chocolate Corporation vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America, Local 464, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    4/5/48. Issue: Seniority--Transfers.
  - Item 5: ACF-Brill Motors Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1263, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    4/9/48. Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure.
  - Item 6: Pennsylvania Sugar, Division of the National Sugar Refining Company vs. Sugar Workers Union No. 1648, affiliated with the International Longshoremen's Association, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    5/26/48. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 7: Franklin Smelting and Refining Company vs. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 42, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    6/21/48. Issue: Retroactive Pay--Arbitrability.
  - Item 8: Florence Pipe Foundry and Machine Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2040, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/13/48. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 9: Hanover Cordage Company vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12680, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    9/18/48. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 10: Continental Can Company, Incorporated, Plant No. 3 (Canonsburg, Pennsylvania) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 215, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    11/3/48. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
  - Item 11: Philadelphia Brick Company (Sharon Hill, Pennsylvania) vs. United Brick and Clay Workers of America, Local 760, 1948; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 3)
    7/9/48. Issue: Rates of Pay--Vacations, Holidays and Holiday Pay.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Albany Manufacturing Company (Interstate Hosiery Company) Albany, GA vs. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Branch 168, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    10/24/49. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 2: Philadelphia Transportation Company vs. Transport Workers Union of Philadelphia, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    6/24/49. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 3: RCA Victor, Division of Radio Corporation of America vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 103, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    6/24/49. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Classification.
  - Item 4: SKF Industries, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    1/27/49. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 5: National Sugar Refining Company vs. Sugar Workers' Union No. 1648, affiliated with the International Longshoremen's Association, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    2/17/49. Issue: Holidays--Election Day.
  - Item 6: Albany Manufacturing Company (Interstate Hosiery Company) Albany, GA, vs. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Branch 168, 1949; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 4)
    1/3/49. Issue: Schedules of Work; Rates of Pay.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1950; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Julius Kayser and Company vs. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1950; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    6/7/50. Issue: Rates of Pay; Fringe Benefits--Pension Plans; Holidays; Insurance.
  - Item 2: Tamaqua Laundry and Dry Cleaning Company vs. United Construction Workers, Local 80, 1950; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    9/14/50. Issue: Contract Negotiation.
  - Item 3: Atlas Power Company, Reynolds Works vs. United Mine Workers of America, District 50, 1950; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 5)
    12/11/50. Issue: Classification of Jobs; Lunch Periods.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: De Laval Steam Turbine Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    9/11/51. Issue: Rates of Pay--Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 2: John A. Roebling's Sons Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2111, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    7/6/51. Issue: Schedules of Work.
  - Item 3: Hanover Cordage Company, Hanover, Pennsylvania vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12680, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    7/23/51. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 4: S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. Warehouse Employees Union, Local 169, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    7/23/51. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 5: Pennsylvania Forge Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists, District Lodge No. 1, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    6/7/51. Issue: Layoff Reinstatement.
  - Item 6: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898, 1951; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 6)
    12/11/51. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1953-1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    12/19/53. Issue: Discharge; Arbitrability.
  - Item 2: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 9/22/53. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 3: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 7/31/53. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 4: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 3/11/52. Issue: Overtime.
  - Item 5: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 3/7/52. Issue: Suspension; Discharge.
  - Item 6: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 5/12/52. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 7: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 7/13/53. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 8: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    2/9/55. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 9: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 4/15/54. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 10: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 10/19/53. Issue: Overtime.
  - Item 11: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 3/24/64. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 12: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1/18/54. Issue: Illness; Working Conditions--In-Plant Temperature.
  - Item 13: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 6/27/66. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 14: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1/17/54. Issue: Incentive Pay.
  - Item 15: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 7/23/63. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 16: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 7/18/55. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 17: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 3/9/55. Issue: Layoff.
  - Item 18: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1/24/55. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 19: SKF Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898., 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 5/12/54. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 20: "To Whom it May Concern Letter" on backlog of cases, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 7)
    4/1/78.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Philadelphia Transportation Company vs. Transport Workers Union of Philadelphia, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    2/8/52. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 1: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation, Eddystone Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    6/2/53. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 2: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation, Eddystone Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Decisions, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: The Budd Company vs. International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4/4/52. Issue: Past Practice--Overtime.
  - Item 3: Keystone Watch Case Division of the Riverside Metal Company vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 139, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    1/14/52. Issue: Discrimination.
  - Item 4: DeLaval Steam Turbine Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3355, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    2/26/52. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Classification.
  - Item 5: Claymont Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3182, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4/30/52. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 6: Jacob Stern and Sons Incorporated vs. Oil Workers International Union, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    11/21/52.Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 7: Pennsylvania Greyhound Lines, Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1063, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    7/28/52. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
  - Item 8: Cutler Metal Products Company vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 134, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4/10/52. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Alan Wood Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1392., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    6/4/53. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 2: Harrisburg Gas Company vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America and Local 12286, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    1/9/53. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 3: Alan Wood Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1392, 1952; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    4/16/52. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 4: Crucible Steel Casting Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3262, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    5/9/53. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 5: Hanover Cordage Company vs. United Mine Workers of America, District 50, Local 12680, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    9/28/53. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 6: Alan Wood Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1392., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    6/4/53. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 7: Alan Wood Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1392., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    6/4/53. Issue: Overtime--Refusal of Overtime.
  - Item 8: Link-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operations vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    7/18/53. Issue: Vacations.
  - Item 9: Link-Belt Company, Philadelphia Operations vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3828, 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    7/18/53. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
  - Item 10: Alan Wood Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1392., 1953; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 10)
    6/4/53. Issue: Insubordination--Refusal of Work Assignment; Discipline; Suspensions.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation, Eddystone Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    5/29/54. Issue: Schedules of Work; Working Conditions--Wash-Up Time.
  - Item 2: Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corporation, Eddystone Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2443, 1954; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 11)
    5/26/54. Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Layoff as Discipline.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    11/3/55. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 2: National Vulcanized Fibre Company vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Fibre and Plastic Local 770, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    7/28/55. Issue: Discipline.
  - Item 3: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    11/17/55. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 4: Gould National Battery Company vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 108, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    11/28/55. Issue: Vacation Pay.
  - Item 5: Owens Yacht Company vs. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 28, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 12)
    9/25/55. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay; Classification of Jobs.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Gould-National Batteries, Incorporated vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    12/13/56. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 2: Donegal Manufacturing Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    2/10/56. Issue: Discharge.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/10/57. Issue: Rates of Pay; Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 2: Warner Company, Cedar Hollow Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    4/9/57. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 3: Melrath Supply and Gasket Company, Incorporated vs. Melrath Employees' Independent Union, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    5/8/57. Issue: Departments; Incentive Pay; Seniority.
  - Item 4: France Packing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    5/31/57. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 5: Florence Pipe Foundry and Machine Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    5/31/57. Issue: Promotion.
  - Item 6: Philadelphia Insulated Wire Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 118, Insulated Wire Workers, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    4/24/57. Issue: Reinstatement; Contracting-Out.
  - Item 7: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/10/57. Issue: Layoffs.
  - Item 8: Advance Specialty Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4993., 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    10/14/57. Issue: Vacation Pay; Reinstatement.
  - Item 9: Advance Specialty Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4993., 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    5/18/57. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 10: Advance Specialty Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4993., 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    2/8/57. Issue: Absences; Rates of Pay.
  - Item 11: Frank S. Nelson and Company, Incorporated vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    11/7/57. Issue: Seniority.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: J. Bishop and Company Platinum Works vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3183, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    12/12/58. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 2: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335., 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 12/2/58. Issue: Vacation Pay.
  - Item 3: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335., 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 12/2/58. Issue: Payroll Deduction.
  - Item 4: Advance Specialty Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4993, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    12/15/58. Issue: Rates of Pay--Minimum Wage Law.
  - Item 5: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335., 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 11/21/58. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 6: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335., 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 12/2/58. Issue: Insurance.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: SKF Industries vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2898, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1/31/58. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Crucible Steel Casting Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    11/16/59. Issue: Rates of Pay.
  - Item 2: Crucible Steel Casting Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3262, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1/2/59. Issue: Reinstatement; Seniority.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Crucible Steel Casting Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    2/13/60. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 2: Penn Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1335, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    11/26/60. Issue: Discrimination.
  - Item 3: American Engineering Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    10/19/60. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 4: Atlas Powder Company vs. District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 13101, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    7/22/60. Issue: Improper Personal Conduct.
  - Item 5: Pennsylvania Malleable Iron Corporation vs. International Molders, and Foundry Workers Union of North America, Local 287, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    10/24/60. Issue: Improper Personal Conduct; Reinstatement.
  - Item 6: Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company, Yale Materials Handling Division vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge No. 1717, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    12/60. Issue: Reinstatement.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: NEAPCO Products, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2479, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)